

**SOFTWARE ENGINEER** 



brett.j.robb@gmail.com



<u> 0450068229</u>

#### Profile

I have spent the last years 13 years developing distributed applications varying from Angular apps to multi-threaded Window Services. My experience ranges from modernising and extending the behaviour of legacy systems to leading greenfield projects from inception through to deployment.

# Employment History

## Software Engineer - Team Lead at ParkIQ

February 2015 - Present · 5 years

- Led a team that developed <u>Watermelon Parking</u> system
- Created Command Switch API which allows users to remotely control car park gates, push real time tariffs and open shutter doors
- Created .Net Core API which modernised legacy scheduled tasks to use QUARTZ Jobs
- Implemented single sign-on API that implements OpenId Connect & OAUTH 2.0
- Modernised web form application to AngularJS & WebAPI 2.0
- Improved software release cycle by automating manual processes
- Used dependency injection and unit tests to improve code quality and assurance
- Introduced pull requests and GIT Flow to my team
- Managed software releases for multiple applications
- Developed numerous car park integrations using third party SDKs

### Software Developer - at Digital Turbine

March 2014 - Janurary 2015 · 11 months

- Modernised legacy system to MVC architecture
- Created application that injected code into APKs to allow subscription payments for EA Sports Android games
- Agile training

### Ballast Train Operator - at Laing O'Rourke

June 2012 - December 2013 · 1 year 7 months

- Ballast Train Operator
- Track Construction
- Track Protection Officer

### Software Engineer - at Step-Up Solutions

March 2009 - May 2012 · 3 years 3 months

- Developed Shift Integration System Shift provides complete car park management, from payment and reconciliation to analysis and reporting
- Developed ParkIQ Web Service solution for updating site information for multiple clients
- · Created scheduled tasks to automatically retrieve car park rates, update shift data and reconcile payment transactions
- Responsible for installing and updating software at over 300 sites throughout Australia, Malaysia and South Africa
- Worked closely with clients to establish system requirement documents
- Strengthened development methodologies by introducing a code quality and code review documents

## Current Languages

.Net Core & Framework C#



AngularJS - Angular 9.0



**JavaScript** 

食食食食

SQL Server - TSQL

SQL Server - Admin

\*\*\*

\*\*\*

### Skills

.Net 2.0 - 4.7.2

.Net Core API

WebAPI 2.0

**MVC** 

Web & Windows Forms

Web Services

**Angular CLI** 

IIS

**Desgin Patterns** 

HTML, JQuery, AJAX & CSS

**Bootstrap & Angular Material** 

**AMCharts & ChartJS** 

**Crystal & Jasper Reports** 

PCI-DSS Level 1 software compliant developer

Visual Studio & Visual Studio Code

Git & SVN

Jira, Source Tree, Bit Bucket & Bamboo

### Links

Linkedin Profile

Watermelon Parking

ParkIQ

**Digital Turbine** 

**Cortell** 

**Download Transcript** 

## Analyst Programmer - at Cortell

January 2009 - Feb 2012 · 1 year 2 months

- Assisted with the design, development and integration of a new accounting system
- Implemented multiple currencies convertor
- · Responsible for writing scripts to T-SQL scripts to create, delete and alter data
- · Designed and implemented client side updates for the system using JavaScript
- Bug fixing after converting the solution from Delphi to C#

## Education

### Waikato Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Information Technology - Top Graduating Student

February 2005 - November 2008

## Francis Douglas Memorial College

January 1994 - December 1999

## Honours and Awards

- Microsoft Certified Professional: Exam 70-483 Programming in C#
- Best Bachelor of Information Technology Project Team award
- School of Information Technology Medal for top graduating student
- Bonded Merit Scholarship recipient for academic achievement
- Straight A Student *Download Transcript*